question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Han Solo's co-pilot and best friend, 'Chewbacca', is an Ewok.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"] },
    { "category": "Entertainment: Film",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004's 'The Aviator'.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": ["True"] },
    { "category": "Entertainment: Film",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": ["False"] },
    { "category": "Entertainment: Film",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "The 2010 film 'The Social Network' is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": ["True"] },
    { "category": "Entertainment: Film",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In the original script of 'The Matrix', the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"] },
    { "category": "Entertainment: Film",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, 'Bad Motherf*cker' in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": ["False"] },
    { "category": "Entertainment: Film",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio's character hunts down the killer of his son.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": ["False"] },
    { "category": "Entertainment: Film",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "The weapon Clint Eastwood uses in 'Dirty Harry' was a .44 Automag.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": ["True"] },
    { "category": "Entertainment: Film",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "YouTube personality Jenna Marbles served as an executive producer of the film Maximum Ride (2016).",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": ["False"] },
    { "category": "Entertainment: Film",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The original ending of 'Little Shop Of Horrors' has the plants taking over the world.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": ["False"] } 
]